<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shubham Nishad</title>
    <link>https://shubhamnishad.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shubham Nishad</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2018 Copyright Text</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 18:31:43 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shubhamnishad.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://shubhamnishad.com/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamnishad.com/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toki-keep a note</title>
      <link>https://shubhamnishad.com/projects/toki/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 14:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamnishad.com/projects/toki/</guid>
      <description>toki-keep-a-note A simple note taking app made with Django. http://toki1.pythonanywhere.com/

Toki is a simple note taking Django project. It was developed to act as a Hands-on and to increase my experience with a MVC framework(MTV as in the case of Django).
I was interested in Django from the first time I searched about and after a little investigation I choose Django as the base for this project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>second</title>
      <link>https://shubhamnishad.com/blog/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 14:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shubhamnishad.com/blog/second/</guid>
      <description>QR-Code-Generator Generate fast and simple QR codes for sharing. Download the extension here
Although this a chrome extension but a web version using the same code is hosted on Github Pages for a quick look. https://shubhamnishad97.github.io/QR-Code-Generator/
I wanted to learn to make extensions from the first time I used one. This extension acted as the perfect idea and hence it was born. This is one part of my QRCode sharing project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>